The thing I don't think people give
Tyler enough credit for is his ability
to sample.
>> Sorry.
I'm sorry I don't see you more.
>> So quickly play the original it comes
from a song called He Made You Mine.
>> When I was a little boy
So
>> just how it has that classic hip-hop
kind of sample feel to it. I thought it
was just a few chops. He actually does
eight chops from the song.
>> [music]
>> And my favorite part and I think what
makes this song really special is that
he sampled this part of the song.
Every time we hear that build-up he gets
into that really aggressive voice.
>> Read the room. Don't assume [music]
[__] is cool. Stay in your pocket.
This is cool.
>> And it makes the song really dynamic
because there's two sides to it and I
think he's playing on this concept of
sorry not sorry because he starts the
song with sincere apologies. He
apologizes to his mom.
>> I'm sorry I don't see you more. I'm
sorry that the four [music] minutes
where you see a song could feel like a
chore.
>> And then he apologizes to his sister who
we don't ever really hear about.
>> So I'm sorry I'm your kid. [music]
Sorry we ain't close as we should have
been.
>> Then he says sorry to Odd Future. He
says sorry to my old friends. Old
friends having the same initials as Odd
Future.
>> Sorry to my old friends. Stories we
could have wrote if our egos didn't take
the pen.
>> So it starts very sincere. By the end of
the song he's doing the sorry not sorry
thing where he's speaking to like people
that criticize him or say that he's
changed.
>> Sorry to the fans who say I changed
[music] cuz I did. Sorry you don't know
me on a personal level to pinpoint where
it
>> And then what really really makes the
song which is the outro where he almost
does like a Kendrick-like switch of
voice and just [__] taking the song
to another level dynamically.
>> I told them I was
>> [music]
>> going to stop [__] around right after
this [__] album. WHY WE NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE FACT THAT I GOT TWO WORDS?
[__] THEM.
>> [music]
>> Super dynamic song. Rapping is great.
Multiple voices, multiple perspectives.
Kind of gives you everything in Tyler
the Creator in one package.